epilogue.net 2011-05-30

# Fantasy Art at Epilogue.net - Privacy Policy - Fantasy and Sci-fi at their best©

At Epilogue, we respect your privacy and take the responsibility of protecting the personal information that you share with us very seriously. To earn your trust and confidence in Epilogue, we are disclosing our privacy practices and the uses of the information that we gather.

These links provide detailed information about Epilogue's privacy policies:

  * What general information does Epilogue collect and how is it used?
  * What personal information does Epilogue collect and how is it used?
  * How do I access, change or delete information about myself?

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or believe that Epilogue has acted in a manner inconsistent with this statement, please send email to [webmaster@epilogue.net](mailto:webmaster@epilogue.net).

Epilogue reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement at any time without notice, and only the current Privacy Statement may be deemed effective.

**What general information does Epilogue collect and how is it used?**

When you visit Epilogue, we collect some basic information about your computer, including:

  * IP address (your computer's unique signature on the internet)
  * Operating system (e.g., Windows 95)
  * Browser software (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape)
  * Internet Service Provider (e.g., AOL)

The information we collect reflects the population as a whole rather than focusing on individuals. We use it to help us better understand the people who visit Epilogue. This information helps us identify the most popular regions on our web site and determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. In addition, we disclose some of this information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and clicked on their advertisements.

**Cookie Usage**  
For security reasons, and to automate login and member profile management, we use a "cookie" to store your Epilogue login information. Certain parts of this cookie will automatically expire 24 hours after login. All this means is that you will have re-enter your login information on the Member Login page if it has been more than a day since your last login.

A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site stores in your Web browser and on your PC. We leave the cookie on your PC so that you will not have to re-enter your username and password on every page of your Member Home Page and Message Center.

You can set up your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set at all. 

**However, if you prevent cookies from being set you will not be able to login!**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

[   
For more information on cookies, please visit ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)<http://help.netscape.com/kb/consumer/19970226-2.html>

**What personal information does Epilogue collect and how is it used?**

When you sign up (or enter contests) at Epilogue, we collect personal identifying information from you, which may include the following:  

  * First and last name;
  * Home or other physical address;
  * E-mail address;
  * Phone number;
  * Any other information that identifies you as a specific individual; and
  * Any other information that, when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual.

Information collected by Epilogue is stored in our database. Only authorized Epilogue employees have access to this information, in a manner consistent with or exceeding industry standards. Remember that third-party vendors also sell products and services on Epilogue, and their policies may differ from those of Epilogue.  Your address, phone number, and email address will NOT be accessible by the general viewing audience, but is required so we may contact you if necessary. Other information about you may be accessible by visitors on your Gallery pages.

We use information about our members and visitors for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our services. We reserve the right to use third parties to provide these services. These third parties may receive certain personal identifying information about you in order for them to perform their services.  

**How do I access, change or delete information about myself?**

When registering for Epilogue membership, we require you to supply basic contact information including your email address. This information is used to maintain and improve our services including email-based services. We may also use this information to contact you with information regarding special events, announcements, contests, etc.

If, at any time, you would no longer wish to receive mailings from Epilogue, simply click on the 'Unsubscribe' link at the bottom of the email. If this is not successful, please contact us at [webmaster@epilogue.net](mailto:webmaster@epilogue.net).

We save your personal information until you are no longer a member of Epilogue. If you would like to remove yourself as an Epilogue member, please email [support@epilogue.net](mailto:support@epilogue.net). Once you've left, we will delete your information from our active database. However, residual information will remain on our archived database and records, but it will not be used for commercial purposes.

**3rd Party Served Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on visits to sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Each 3rd party company has its own privacy practices and policies. Follow these links for more information:
